Tang Zhiluo, are you still going to run away?
Zhiluo.
Why isn't Su Zhiye here yet?
I heard from the Su family's servants
that he left this morning
and hasn't returned yet.
Did he say when he would be back?
He only said he was going to a banquet at Huizhen Pavilion.
Send someone to Prince Yu's Mansion.
Have him pass a message to Princess Xiyao for me.
If Prince Yu wants to eliminate Jingxuan's right-hand man,
he doesn't have to go this far.
Yuwen Jingxuan.
He is not worth me doing this.
Hahaha.
What are you laughing at?
So that's how it is.
I'm laughing because Prince Yu has exhausted all his schemes,
yet still couldn't resist the charm of a beauty.
Su Zhiye.
You were the one who handed her over to me personally.
It's easy to mend clothes.
But trust between people is hard to mend.
Your Highness, I am from beyond the Great Wall.
I really don't understand the hidden meanings of you Central Plains people.
I'll just speak my mind.
That makes me seem less straightforward.
I hope you can release Su,
Young Master Su.
Yuwen Jingxuan told you, didn't he?
In what capacity are you saying this?
Princess Consort Yu,
or Princess of Rouran?
As Xiyao.
Not the Princess of Rouran,
nor Princess Consort Yu.
If you want the right to negotiate with me,
I'm afraid there is only one thing
that can be used as a bargaining chip.
I really overestimated you, Your Highness.
Overestimated?
Giving what you gave to Su Zhiye
to me,
you call that overestimating?
Meeting you
was like a dream.
I will remember it forever.
Oh.
Smell this.
Smell it.
I will give myself to you.
Zhiluo.
What's wrong?
Yuwen Jingxuan,
I remember now.
After all we've been through,
this is the first time
I've looked at you so carefully.
I remember everything.
Don't think too much.
As long as we are together,
there is always a way.
We were one step behind after all.
If I hadn't been poisoned, maybe...
Don't say such things.
We haven't reached a dead end yet.
Shang Zaiyi has been plotting for years,
and has the Imperial Preceptor's guidance behind him.
I can make a risky move.
But you can't.
Zhiluo,
don't you understand yet?
In my heart,
neither imperial power nor my life
is as important as you.
What about the people of the world?
Are you really going to let someone like Yuwen Jia...
To decide the fate of the people in the world?
I'm going out for a bit.
Get some rest.
The prince received a note.
Just as I thought.
To take my life,
Yuwen Jia will stop at nothing.
I'll go with you.
Trust me.
Yuwen Jia, you broke your promise.
What kind of person do you think I am, Princess?
Aren't you afraid of the Su family?
As long as I kill Yuwen Jingxuan,
the whole world will be mine.
Are we afraid of the Su family?
Burn it.
Stop.
You came at the right time, Sixth Brother.
I'm here.
You can let them go now, Brother.
There's no rush.
Zhiluo.
Sixth Brother.
There are more ways to control a person's mind in this world
than just the Soul-Destroying Nail.
Kill him.
Stop.
Prince Yu,
I won the bet.
You couldn't bear to let me die.